Class of 1925 Records, 1921-1995
Smith College Archives
Class of 1925 Records
1921-1995
Smith College. Class of 1925.
RG 80
13 boxes (18.5 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1925.
Historical Note
The Class of 1925 was the forty-seventh graduating class of Smith College.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Class of 1925 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1925, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1925 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Commencement 1925 (Box 1972, Folder 1)
- Commencement Music 1925 (Box 1972, Folder 2)
- Commencement Photographs 1925 (Box 1972, Folder 3)
- Commencement Speaker 1925 (Box 1972, Folder 4)
- Freshman Frolic 1921 (Box 1972, Folder 5)
- Freshman Handbook 1921-1922 (Box 1972, Folder 6)
- General 1925 (Box 1972, Folder 7)
- Groups 1921-1925 (Box 1972, Folder 8)
- History n.d. (Box 1972, Folder 9)
- Ivy Day 1925 (Box 1972, Folder 10)
- Ivy Day-Photographs 1925 (Box 1972, Folder 11)
- Junior Prom 1924 (Box 1972, Folder 12)
- Junior Ushers 1924 (Box 1972, Folder 13)
- Class Letters 1934-1984 (Box 1972, Folder 14)
- Class Notes 1966-1975 (Box 1972, Folder 15)
- Senior Dramatics 1925 (Box 1972, Folder 16)
- Senior Dramatics-Photographs 1925 (Box 1972, Folder 17)
- Songs n.d. (Box 1972, Folder 18)
- Sophomore Carnival 1923 (Box 1972, Folder 19)
- Step Sing 1925 (Box 1972, Folder 20)
- Class Supper 1925 (Box 1972, Folder 21)
- Reunions 1930 (Box 1973, Folder 1)
- Reunions 1935 (Box 1973, Folder 2)
- Reunions 1940 (Box 1973, Folder 3)
- Reunions 1945 (Box 1973, Folder 4)
- Reunions 1950 (Box 1973, Folder 5)
- Reunions 1955 (Box 1973, Folder 6)
- Reunions 1960 (Box 1973, Folder 7)
- Reunions 1965 (Box 1973, Folder 8)
- Reunions 1970 (Box 1973, Folder 9)
- Reunions 1975 (Box 1973, Folder 10)
- Reunions 1970-1980 (Box 1973, Folder 11)
- Reunions 1980-1985 (Box 1973, Folder 12)
- Reunions 1995 (Box 1973, Folder 13)
- Reunions-Photographs n.d. (Box 1973, Folder 14)
- Reunions-Songs n.d. (Box 1973, Folder 15)
- Reunion Costume (Box OV)